<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CI-CD | Hugo Academic CV Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ci-cd/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/ci-cd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>CI-CD</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>CI-CD</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ci-cd/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>26-31.05.2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The past week at university was busy and productive. I actively attended lectures and seminars, paying special attention to difficult topics that required extra time to understand. I focused especially on preparing for upcoming tests — reviewing key concepts, solving practical problems, and analyzing mistakes to avoid them in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I participated in group projects, which helped improve my teamwork skills and deepen my understanding of the subjects through discussions with classmates. In my free time, I engaged in self-study by exploring additional literature and materials, which broadened my horizons and better prepared me for exams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the intense schedule, I tried to maintain a balance between studying and rest to keep a high level of motivation and productivity. Overall, the week went well, and I feel confident in my knowledge and ready for new challenges in my studies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CI-CD?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CI/CD is not just trendy abbreviations but key practices for modern software development. They enable teams to build and release software faster, more reliably, and with fewer errors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ci-continuous-integration&#34;&gt;CI (Continuous Integration):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developers regularly integrate their code changes into a shared repository.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automated builds and tests run with every integration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Issues are detected early, making them easier to fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;cd-continuous-deliverydeployment&#34;&gt;CD (Continuous Delivery/Deployment):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automates the process of delivering code changes to various environments (testing, staging, production).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous Delivery: Changes are ready to be deployed to production at any time but require manual approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous Deployment: Changes are automatically deployed to production after passing all tests successfully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-summary-cicd-allows-you-to&#34;&gt;In summary, CI/CD allows you to:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accelerate the release of new features and updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve code quality through automated testing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduce risks associated with deployments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the development process more predictable and efficient.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
